

# Kyle Wagner

Marketing Manager & Visual Designer

#### ABOUT ----

Bangkok, Thailand +66 80-362-0972 kylewag@me.com kyle.coffee 1991-11-22

# EDUCATION -

MA Geography York University, Toronto

BA International Studies DePaul University, Chicago

## SOCIAL -

in kyledwagner

y kyledwagner

**O** kyledwagner

**(C)** +66 80 362 0972

#### LANGUAGES -

 English
 ● ● ● ● ●

 Japanese
 ● ● ○ ○ ○

 Thai
 ● ● ○ ○ ○

 Lao
 ● ● ○ ○ ○

#### SUMMARY

Marketing and communications manager, digital designer and content creator with over five years of experience working with DMCs, Hotels, and NGOs. Creative, analytical and collaborative with international teams. Proficient in web design, branding, PR, content writing, campaigns, and email marketing.

#### EXPERTISE -

Photoshop	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$	Sketch	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
Illustrator	$\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\bullet$ $\circ$	HTML/CSS	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$
InDesign	$\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$	Javascript	•0000
Adoba XD			

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE -

## Marketing Manager @ Outpost January 2020 - Current

Bangkok, Thailand

- Lead our remote team to design collateral for digital events and manage B2C social media posts (including stories).
- Launched paid media campaigns in January & February that gave us our highest ROAS of 9.6 with over \$15,000 generated from ads.
- Concepted and launched an organic campaign during Covid-19 that resulted in 9 non-refundable purchases averaging \$499 per consumer.

# Marketing Manager @ Focus Asia December 2017 - January 2020

Luang Prabang, Laos

- Created, executed and optimized email marketing strategy with 2x weekly send rate; yielded ~20% OR with ~5% CTR.
- Lead marketing team to redesign and rewrite 250pg travel catalogue for increased ROI.
- Rebranded luxury travel sub-brand including website development, logotype design and all marketing collaterals.

# Web Designer & Developer @ TYPE-C 2018 - 2019 (Freelance)

Remote

- Programmed 2 microsites and designed social media ads for a campaign promoting Laos to the Singaporean market.
- Designed and coded three websites using the SquareSpace platform for clients in Singapore.
- Designed a postcard concept for a video production company in Toronto.

# Marketing Coordinator @ Tiger Trail Travel September 2014 - September 2017 (3 Years)

Luang Prabang, Laos

- Redesigned visual communication platform including print-based signage, tour catalogues, brochures, logos, posters, business cards, and newsletters.
- Developed and produced original content for two responsive brand websites: Fairtrek.org and Biking-Laos.com.
- Conceptualized and executed an effective marketing plan, social media strategy, and brand presentation.